mortgage101.com 2008-06-08

# Privacy Policy

| About Mortgage101  

* * *  
  
---  
**About Us**   
Learn about Mortgage101 and our services  
**Contact**   
Mortgage101.com phone numbers and email forms  
**Feedback**   
Tell us what you think about the site  
**Privacy Policy**   
We respect your privacy and value your trust  
**Legal Notice**   
Please read before using the site  
**Site Map **   
Link to resources, tools, and pages on the site  
  |  Mortgage101.com ("Site")   

**Privacy Statement**

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.

By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This Site contains links to other sites. These include links to individual lender/broker sites that offer consumer and business loans, as well links to other third party sites that offer credit reports, property valuation information, insurance quotes, etc. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Browsing the Site**

If you browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the date and time you access our site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site.

**Information Collected**

We collect the email addresses of consumers who communicate with us or through our authorized vendors via email. We also collect information provided to us by consumers in loan or refinance requests submitted through our site or our authorized vendors’ sites ("Loan Request Information"). Loan Request Information typically includes name, address, and phone numbers, email address, household income, estimated credit rating, and loan specific information including but not limited to estimated property value, desired loan amount, downpayment, and whether the applicant is working with a real estate agent. In addition, consumers who express a desire to apply for a loan provide us with and authorize us or our affiliate websites to obtain from third parties necessary financial information such as credit reports ("Finance Information"). We do not provide financing, but instead transmit those requests to third-party vendors for consideration.

All information provided by consumers in any of the above-listed ways or otherwise becomes the property of Internet Brands once received by us and may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy.

Loan Request Information is used to transmit financing requests to third parties who may be in a position to respond to your request. Consumers who submit Loan Request Information expressly authorize up to four (4) third party lenders to contact them by phone or email in connection with their loan or refinancing request regardless of whether or not such consumer is listed on a "Do Not Call" list.

As part of the request process, we may verify the information you provide, or obtain omitted address or other contact information from third parties.

Loan Request Information transmitted to a lender or other fulfillment entity becomes the property of that lender of fulfillment entity, in addition to us. The information is used to process your financing application.

We also share your personal information with our affiliated companies in order to identify products or services in which you may have interest, to improve our user experience and generally to engage in market research and for other internal business purposes. We may also aggregate your personal information with others’ information and prepare reports on site usage, purchase history or other factors for sale or distribution to others. Those reports are aggregated and include no personally identifying information. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.

You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to this Site, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request.

If you prefer for us not to provide your name and email or postal address to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please contact us at .

**Cookies**

We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about you more than once.

**Updating or deleting your information**

You may update or delete your information at any time prior to submitting your completed loan request. Once your loan form is completed and submitted, you will not be able to change any of the information. Additionally, please be advised that once you have submitted your loan request and the information has been received by the lenders/brokers, this information is no longer under our control.

Due to federal & state regulations, we are required to keep a copy of your information for a period of 3 years. Over this period we will maintain all such data in a confidential and secure area that third parties will not be allowed to access.

**Security**

This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this website and other sites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), to serve ads to you on this site and other sites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

In addition, we use clear GIFs or pixel tags to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs enable our ad serving company to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site. This allows us to learn which banner ads bring users to our website. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

To learn more about these practice and your choices about not having this information used by these companies please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

**Contacting the Web Site**

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at out website, so be sure to check back here frequently.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

**Mortgage101.com**

December 1st, 2007

|
